

DEVOPS ENGINEER · SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

1307 West University Ave., Champaign IL 61821

□ (850) 461-8381 | Marrisongtotty@gmail.com | Aharrisontotty.github.io | DharrisonTotty | Tharrisont

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary.

Current Site Reliability Engineer at start-up company Kasa. 7+ years experience specializing in the backend development, infrastructure automation, and computer hacking/security. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience _____

Wolfram Research, Inc.

Champaign, IL

DEVOPS ENGINEER

Apr 2018 - Present

- Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.
- Built fully automated CI/CD pipelines on CircleCI for containerized applications using Docker, AWS ECR and Rancher.
- Designed an overall service architecture and pipelines of the Machine Learning based Fashion Tagging API SaaS product with the micro-services architecture.
- Implemented several API microservices in Node.js Koa and in the serverless AWS Lambda functions.
- Deployed a centralized logging environment (ELK, Filebeat, CloudWatch, S3) which gather log data from docker containers and AWS resources.
- Deployed a centralized monitoring environment(Grafana, InfluxDB, CollectD) which gather system metrics as well as docker run-time metrics.

Wolfram Research, Inc. Champaign, IL

WEB SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR

Dec 2016 - Apr 2018

- Implemented RESTful API server for car rental booking application (CARPLAT in Google Play).
- Built and deployed overall service infrastructure utilizing Docker container, CircleCI, and several AWS stack(Including EC2, ECS, Route 53, S3, CloudFront, RDS, ElastiCache, IAM), focusing on high-availability, fault tolerance, and auto-scaling.
- · Developed an easy-to-use Payment module which connects to major PG(Payment Gateway) companies in Korea.

Wolfram Research, Inc. Champaign, IL

WEB SYSTEMS INTERN

Sep 2016 - Dec 2016

- Lead engineer on agent-less backtracking system that can discover client device's fingerprint(including public and private IP) independently of the Proxy, VPN and NAT.
- Implemented a distributed web stress test tool with high anonymity.
- Implemented a military cooperation system which is web based real time messenger in Scala on Lift.

Tallahassee Community College

Tallahassee, FL

MATHEMATICS AND TECHNOLOGY TUTOR

May 2016 - Aug 2016

- Developed in Cocos2d-x an action puzzle game(Dragon Buster) targeting U.S. market.
- Implemented API server which is communicating with game client and In-App Store, along with two other team members who wrote the game logic and designed game graphics.
- Won the 2nd prize in final evaluation.

Education

ASSOCIATES OF SCIENCE

Tallahassee Community College

Tallahassee, FL

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

Graduated honors with 4.0 GPA.